The problem appears to be unsolvable.
问题看来是解不出了
Maybe we could run some
computer simulations.
做电脑模拟试试呢
There are too many variables.
It would take forever.
变量太多 一辈子都弄不完
We've got to be missing something.
肯定漏下啥了
Let's start again.
咱重来一次
The movie is playing here at 7:20, here
at 7:40, here at 8:10 and here at 8:45.
电影在这是7:20上映 这是7:40
这是8:10 这里是8:45
- These theaters have to be eliminated.
- Why?
- 这些影院要排除掉
- 为啥?
They're state-of-the-art digital
projection, 20-channel surround sound.
这有最先进的数码放映机
20通路环绕立体声
Yes, but they have no Icee machines.
是 但那没有冰吸饮料机
Despite my aggressive
letter-writing campaign, I might add.
还无视我的写信抗议 顺便说一下
What about the multiplex
here? The seats are terrific.
这个多功能影厅怎么样? 座位舒服极了
They have Twizzlers
instead of Red Vines.
那的绳子糖是Twizzlers牌而不是Red Vines的
No amount of lumbar support
can compensate for that.
坐着腰部再舒服也无法弥补
Well, it's gonna take
at least an hour to eat,
吃饭至少要花上一小时
and I don't see a Sheldon-approved restaurant
proximate to a Sheldon-approved theater.
咋就找不到Sheldon许可餐厅
和Sheldon许可影院挨着那种呢
- We could eat after the movie.
- Unacceptable.
- 咱可以看完再吃
- 不可以
The delay would result in tomorrow
morning's bowel movement occurring at work.
晚吃饭的话 明早工作时该想排便了
Hang on, hang on.
There's a 7-Eleven here.
别急 别急 这有个7-11便利店
We smuggle Srpies, which are
essentially Icees, in under our coats,
我们把思乐冰雪泥藏衣服里带进去
就当做冰吸果饮
after having a pleasant meal
either here, here or here.
之前呢 先在这 这或这饱餐一顿
I don't see how we missed that.
刚才咋没发现呢
Excuse me, in what
universe are Slurpies Icees?
打扰一下 啥时候思乐冰雪泥
成了冰吸果饮的一种了?
That's how we missed it.
所以没发现呗
Sheldon, would you be prepared,
on a non-precedential basis,
Sheldon 你能不能就破例一次
to create an emergency ad
hoc Slurpie-Icee equivalency?
紧急临时把这俩饮品等同看待?
Oh, Leonard, you know I can't do that.
哦 Leonard 你知道我做不到
Okay, I guess we only have one option.
好了 看来只有一个法子了
Yep, I don't see any way around it.
是啊 别无他法
- Bye, Sheldon.
- See ya.
- 拜 Sheldon
- 再见
Stay loose.
不用送
They're right, it was the only option.
他们没错 就这一个办法了
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
-=伊甸园美剧http://sfile.ydy.com=-
荣誉出品
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
sync:咔肉肉
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=-
翻译/校对: penny
时间轴: 咔肉肉
双语:徐小帆
The Big Bang
Theory Season02 Episode14
天才理论传
第二季 第14集
Ooh, ooh, shut the door, shut the door.
噢噢 关门 关门
- Why?
- Just do it!
- 为啥?
- 关就是了!
- Get inside and shut the door.
- Well, you didn't specify.
- 进来再关门
- 你又没说清楚
Is Leonard around?
Leonard在吗?
He went to the movies without me.
他去看电影了 没带上我
It was the only option.
只有这样子才行
I'm sorry, I don't understand
which social situation this is.
抱歉 我还没搞清是什么状况
Could you give me some
guidance as to how to proceed?
你能给点指示告诉我接下来干啥吗?
The building manager's showing an apartment
downstairs, and I haven't paid my rent.
大楼管理人在楼下介绍房子呢
我还没付房租
Oh, I see.
哦 明白了
Penny, I'm not sure I'm comfortable harboring a
fugitive from the 2311 North Los Robles Corporation.
Penny 我好像不太喜欢私藏
北Los Robles公寓楼2311号逃犯
It's no big deal.I'm just
a little behind on my bills
没啥大不了的 我就是有点缺钱
because they cut back my hours at
the restaurant and my car broke down.
因为他们削减了我的上班时间
而且我的车还坏了
If you recall, I pointed out the "check
engine" light to you several months ago.
你还记得的话 几个月前我跟你
提过"检查引擎"指示灯的事
The "check engine" light is
fine. It's still blinking away.
"检查引擎"的灯没事 还闪啊闪呢
It's the stupid engine
that stopped working.
是那倒霉引擎坏掉了
It cost me like $1,200 to fix it.
花了我1200块去修
You know, it occurs to me you could solve
all your problems by obtaining more money.
知道么 我突然想到
你可以挣更多钱来解决这些问题
Yes, it occurs to me, too.
是哈 我也想到了
Hang on a moment.
等下
Here. Take some. Pay
me back when you can.
来 拿点吧 有钱了再还
Wow, you got a lot of money in there.
哇 里面钱还不少啊
That's why it's guarded by snakes.
所以才派蛇来看守嘛
- Take some.
- Don't be silly.
- 拿点吧
- 别犯傻了
I'm never silly.
我才不傻
- Here.
- No, I can't.
- 拿着
- 不 不行
Don't you need money?
你不是需要钱吗?
- Well, yeah, but...
- This is money I'm not using.
- 需要 但是...
- 这些钱我用不着
But what if you need it?
那用得上时咋办?
My expenses account for 46.
9% of my after-tax income.
我的花销占我税后工资的46.9%
The rest is divvied up between
a small savings account,
其他钱就分摊给小的储蓄帐户
this deceptive container
of peanut brittle
也就是这个糊弄人的花生脆罐子
and the hollowed-out buttocks
of a superhero action figure
还有一个超级英雄手办
被掏空的屁股
who shall remain nameless
for his own protection.
为了他的安全起见将继续隐姓埋名
Or her own protection.
或者说为了她的安全起见
- Take some.
- Really? I mean, are you sure?
- 拿点吧
- 真的? 你确定?
I see no large upcoming expenditures
unless they develop an affordable technology
我看不会有什么大的开销
除非发明了负担得起的科技
to fuse my skeleton with
adamantium like Wolverine.
可以让我的骨骼坚硬 像金刚狼一样
Are th working on that?
真在发明这个?
I sincerely hope so.
我是真心希望
Okay. Well, thank you.
好吧 谢谢
Oh, no, I can't.
哦 不 我不能要
Sheldon honey, I don't want
things to be weird between us.
Sheldon亲爱的
我不想把咱俩关系搞得怪怪的
Won't it also be weird if I have to say
hello to you every morning on my way to work
那我每天早晨上班路上都要和你打招呼
and you're living in a refrigerator box
and washing your hair with rain water?
你要住在冰箱里 用雨水洗头
这样怪不怪呢?
I'll pay you back as soon as I can.
我一有钱就还给你
Of course you will.
那是当然
It's impossible to pay me
back sooner than you can.
你还没钱呢就还我是不可能的嘛
Assuming you subscribe to a linear
understanding of time and causality.
猜你应该同意时间和因果的线性理论
I'm regretting this already.
我已经开始后悔了
You know, I've given
the matter some thought,
我考虑了一下那个问题
and I think I'd be willing to be a house
pet to a race of super-intelligent aliens.
我想我愿意做高智商外星人的宠物
Interesting.
有意思
Ask me why.
问问我为什么
Do I have to?
必须问啊?
Of course. That's how you
move a conversation forward.
当然了 这样才能继续对话啊
Why?
为什么呢?
The learning opportunities
would be abundant.
将会有很多学习的机会
Additionally, I like
having my belly scratched.
还有呢 我喜欢人家挠我肚肚
Hey, Penny. How was work?
嘿 Penny 工作咋样?
Grt. I hope I'm a waitress at the
Cheesecake Factory for my whole life.
棒极了 真希望一辈子都做蛋糕店的服务员
Was that sarcasm?
这是说反话吗?
No.
不是
Was that sarcasm?
这是说反话吗?
Yes.
是的
- Was that
sar-- - Stop it!
- 这是说反话...
- 打住吧!
Penny, you appear to
have a package here.
Penny 你有一个包裹
Oh, thanks. This must
be the beret I ordered.
哦 谢谢 肯定是我订的贝雷帽
A couple of months ago.
It was back-ordered.
几个月前订的 延期交货
Did you know the beret is an example of piece of
women's fashion adapted from male military uniforms?
知道不 贝雷帽是由男性军装
演变来的女性时尚之一?
Another fascinating
example is the epaulet.
还有个好例子就是肩章
He's not lying. He does
find that fascinating.
他说真的 他真觉得那玩意不错
Okay, whatever.
好了 随便了
It's not like I'm running up and down
the streets just buying myself berets.
我又不是到处跑 只为买贝雷帽
I bought one, like, a month
ago, and it was back-ordered.
我买了一顶 n个月前买的
还是延期交货
Look, it finally arrived, all right?
瞧着 终于来了 好吗?
- All right.
- Oh, my God, would you just get off my case?
- 好吧
- 哦 天啊 你能别理我了不?
Weird.
怪哦
Oh, good, that was an unusual
interaction. I wasn't sure.
哦 是啊 这次交流的确别扭
我还不确定呢
Did you guys have an argument?
你俩吵架了?
No.
没有
Well, you clearly did
something to aggravate her.
你肯定做啥事惹着她了
I'm at a loss.
我糊涂了都
If you like, you can review my
daily log of social interactions
你愿意的话 可以看看我的每日交际记录
and see if there's a
blunder I overlooked.
看有没啥大错被我忽视了
Here you go.
给你
Oh, you owe me another two dollars.
The price of moo shu pork went up.
对了 你欠我两块钱 木须肉涨价了
It's getting tougher and
tougher to be a bad Jew.
做个坏犹太人越来越难了
Here you go, Penny.
Shrimp with lobster sauce.
你的 Penny 带龙虾酱的虾
Thank you, Leonard. What's my share?
谢了 Leonard 我的多少钱?
Don't worry about it. It's my treat.
算了 我请客
- No, really, how much?
- It's... hatever. $10, $11.
- 不 说真的 多少钱?
- 10块还是11块吧
Well, which is it, $10 or $11?
到底多少 10还是11?
14.50 But it's no biggie.
14.5 不算什么啦
You'll get the next one.
下次你请
What?
笑啥?
He was just wondering if he wo
skintight jeans and a tank top
他在想要是他也穿紧身仔裤吊带背心
if he'd get his shrimp lo mein for free.
他的虾捞面是不是也免费
What are you saying?
说什么呢?
That I'm using my body to get dinner?
我利用自己的身体换饭吃?
That I'm some kind of
Chinese food prostitute?
我是中餐妓女啊?
Yeah, Raj, what are you saying?
就是 Raj 咋说话呢?
'Cause let me tell you something, buddy.
我告诉你们 兄弟们
I pay my own way in this world, okay?
我自己花自己的钱 好不?
I don't rely on anybody!
我不靠任何人!
What was that about?
咋跑了?
He has a nervous bladder
when he's stressed out.
他一紧张 膀胱就受不了
Kind of like a puppy.
跟狗狗差不多
Here, Leonard--
$10, $11, $12...
给你 Leonard 10 11 12...14块钱
It was $14. 50, but it's okay.
是14块5 但没事的
Oh, good. Dinner's here.
哦 太好了 晚饭来了
Yes, dinner's here, and I'm having
some. I'm having takeout food.
是的 有晚饭吃 我在吃 我在吃外带食品
- Okay.
- You're damn right it's okay.
- 好吧
- 你算是说对了
I've been having leftovers at
the restaurant for like four days,
我在餐馆吃了4天剩饭了
and I wanted something
different. So sue me.
我想吃点不一样的 咋了 去告我呀
Forgive me, Penny, but that would be the
very definition of a frivolous lawsuit.
恕我直言 Penny 那可就是纯粹的琐碎案了
Sheldon, look, I will pay
you back as soon as I can.
Sheldon 听着 我一有钱就还你
You just have to give me more time.
你得多给我点时间
Oh, wait, you lent her money?
等等 你借她钱了?
She needed money.
她需要钱
You seem under pressure. Did I
not lend you a sufficient amount?
你看起来很有负担 我借你的钱不够?
Because I n give you more.
我还可以多给你点
Oh, you know, you would just
love that, wouldn't you? Yeah.
哦 你就爱施舍是吧?
You would just love to open
up your little snake can
你就喜欢打开那小蛇罐子
and throw some money at the
girl who can't pay her bills.
把钱丢给付不起账单的女孩
Where are you going?
你去哪啊?
Going home, where I won't be
interrogated like a criminal.
回家 我可不想被当做犯人审了
I forgot my fortune cookie.
忘拿福饼了
In case either of you
have larceny in your heart,
提前跟心怀鬼胎的人说
you should know that I've moved
my money out of the snake can.
我的钱已经不在小蛇罐子里了
But if you're ever short, there's always
a couple of 50s in Green Lantern's ass.
你们要是啥时候缺钱
绿灯侠的屁股里永远藏着几张50的
A little mood lighting, huh?
蛮有情调哈?
Yeah.When I didn't pay my bill,
是啊 我没付账单
the Department of Water and Power
thought I would enjoy the ambience.
水电局觉得我会喜欢这氛围
Yeah, they're very considerate that way.
是啊 他们还真体贴
I used Sheldon's money to pay my rent.
我用Sheldon的钱付了房租
Then I had like $14 left over.
然后剩下14块吧
$14, huh?
14块哦?
Put it back in your pocket, or I'll
find some other place to put it.
放回口袋里 要不我找地方塞
Back in the pocket it goes.
放回口袋啦
Look, you do understd that Sheldon really
doesn't care when he gets the money back.
你该知道Sheldon并不在意你啥时候还钱
It's actually one of the few idiosyncrasies that
doesn't make you want to, you know, kill him.
说实话 是他少有的几个好地方之一
让人不那么想...杀了他
Yeah, well, that's not
really my big problem.
那倒不是我的大问题
So you're a little behind on your bills.
Everybody gets behind on their bills.
你缺钱 付不起账单嘛
人人都有这样的时候
Yeah, I know, it's just...
this wasn't the plan.
是 我知道 只是...计划不是这样的
It wasn't supposed to go this way.
不该这样嘛
Well, what was the plan?
计划是什么样的?
Um, waitress for six months
and then become a movie star.
做六个月服务员 然后成为电影明星
Was there a plan B?
有没后备计划?
TV star.
电视明星
It's probably not as bad as
you think. Let's take a look.
或许没你想的那么糟 我们看看
Maybe we can find some corners to cut.
也许能找到省钱的法子呢
Oh, here's something.
看这个
If you don't have electricity,
then you probably don't need cable.
你要是没电的话 也就用不上有线电视了
Just a suggestion.
提议而已
$170 dollars for acting classes?
170美元的表演课?
Oh, no, I can't give
up my acting classes.
不行 表演课绝对不能省
I'm a professional actress.
我是职业演员
You've had an acting
job where you got paid?
你有能进账的表演工作了?
That is not the
definition of professional.
职业不是这么定义的
Actually, it kind of...
Let's keep looking.
其实吧 有点...咱接着看
Whoa, what's $1,800 to the Los
Angeles County Superior Court?
喔 洛杉矶高级法庭的1800块怎么回事?
Oh, that's nothing.
哦 没什么
Nothing? It sounds like you got caught
speeding going 4,000 miles an hour.
没什么? 这么多钱感觉像你
以每小时4千英里超速被捕呢
Well, remember Kurt?
记得Kurt吗?
Your ex-boyfriend?
你前男友?
Yeah. He got arrested for
taking a whiz on a cop car.
嗯 他在警车上撒尿被抓了
- What?
- He was drunk.
- 啥?
- 他喝多了
I would hope so.
我猜也是
Anyway, he had a bunch of outstanding
tickets and a bench warrant,
总之 他收了一堆罚单和一张拘票
so I, you know, I paid his fines.
我...替他付了罚款
Did he pay you back?
他还你没有?
No, but he will.
没 但他会还的
And that's based on the inherent
credit-worthiness of people
你信那与生俱来值得信赖
who get drunk and urinate
on police vehicles?
喝得醉醺醺 在警车上撒尿的人?
Leonard, I'm not gonna call
up Kurt and ask him for money.
Leonard 我才不会打电话给Kurt
找他要钱呢
Well... what are you gonna do?
那你怎么办?
I don't know, but I may have
to find a cheaper place to live.
不知道 或许得找个便宜的地方住
Oh, no...
不要啊
Oh, you don't want to do that.
你不能搬啊
Why not?
为什么不?
Moving is a big deal.
搬家可是大事
You have to go to the
supermarket and get boxes,
你得去超市 找盒子
and if they're not clean, then your books
smell like melons, and it's just, like...
要是盒子不干净 你的书会有西瓜味...
Why don't you just get
a roommate a stay here?
干嘛不找个室友来 继续住这里?
Well, do you know anybody?
你有认识人吗?
Well, I'm sure the guy living with
Sheldon wouldn't mind moving in with you.
敢肯定Sheldon的室友不介意搬过来
Oh, Leonard, honey, if we
started living together,
Leonard 亲爱的 要是我们住在一起
I wouldn't be able to
keep my hands off you.
我可就离不开你了
Really?
真的?
And you thought my acting
lessons were a waste of money.
你还说我报表演课是浪费钱
This moo shu pork's burning
a hole through my duodenum.
木须肉要把我十二指肠烧穿了
Leviticus 11:3: "Only that which parteth the hoof
and cheweth the cud among the beasts shall ye eat."
利未记 第十一章第三节
"凡蹄分两瓣 倒嚼的走兽 你们都可以吃"
Hey, do I mock you with the Bhagavad-Gita
every time you scarf down a Whopper?
嘿 你每次吞下大汉堡时
我嘲笑过"巴哥维得・吉它"没?
Hey, what's going on?
嘿 咋样?
We're on a quest through the Valley
of Fire to acquire the sacred crown.
我们在火之山谷探寻圣冠
You want the Valley of
Fire? It's right here.
想找火之山谷? 就在这呢
Hey, you guys want to
go on a real live quest?
嘿 你们想不想来个真正的探险?
Outside? I just made cocoa.
外出啊? 我刚做了可可
- Come on. It'll be fun.
- What is it?
- 来吧 肯定有意思
- 啥事啊?
Do you guys remember
Penny's ex-boyfriend Kurt?
还记得Penny的前男友Kurt吗?
Yeah, that's him.
对 就是他
It tur out he owes Penny a lot of
money, and I'm gonna go get it from him.
原来他欠Penny很多钱
我想去找他要回来
Who's with me?
谁跟我走?
Ooh, double sixes.
哦 两个六
Really? You're just
gonna let me go by myself?
真的啊? 你们就让我自己去?
Oh, cool, I got a sword.
哦 太棒了 我得到了剑
I could use some help.
我需要帮忙
Here.
给你
You guys are unbelievable.
你们真是叫我无语
You play a game to simulate adventure,
你们玩模拟的探险游戏
but when there's real adventure out there
in the real world, you just wimp out.
现在真有探险了吧 你们又怂了
Leonard, do you not recall the last time we visited
this gentleman, we returned home without pants?
Leonard 还记得上次去拜访这位绅士吗
回来时连裤子都没有了?
- I do.
- Are you sure?
- 记得
- 真记得?
Because your proposal
suggests that you don't.
听这提议感觉你忘了呢
- I'm not afraid of him.
- All right. Leonard fairly calls the question:
- 我不怕他
- 好吧 Leonard提出了一个问题
Who is in favor of abandoning our game and
confronting Penny's steroid-infused ex-boyfriend
谁想放下手中的游戏 加入到对峙
Penny打鸡血的前男友的
in a suicidal mission to
extract money from him?
自杀性讨债任务中去?
Say hi to Kurt for us.
替我们给Kurt带好
Excuse me.
听我说
When Frodo left the Shire to
take the one ring to Mordor,
当弗拉多离开夏尔 拿着戒指到魔多时
didn't Samwise, Pippin
d Merry go with him?
山姆怀斯 皮平和梅利没跟他一起去?
- They did.
- Well?
- 去了
- 那你们呢
They had a terrible time of it, Leonard.
他们可是受尽苦啊 Leonard
Plus, no one stole their pants.
而且没人偷他们裤子
Fine. Enjoy your little game.
I'll make this quest on my own.
好吧 享受你们的小游戏吧
我自己去找他
Leonard, wait.
Leonard 等等
Take a jacket. It's shpritzing a little.
穿个外套 有点小雨
You guys suck.
你们怂死了
Come on, please? He's so big.
来嘛 拜托了? 他块头太大
Okay, is everyone clear on the plan?
好了 计划都清楚了?
Yes. Koothrappali's going to
wet himself, I'm gonna throw up,
是的 Koothrappali会尿裤子 我会吐
Sheldon's gonna run away,
and you're going to die.
Sheldon会跑掉 你会死翘翘
Shall we synchronize our watches?
对一下时间?
Guys, there are four
of us and one of him.
伙计们 我们有4个人 他才一个
Which means his triumph
will be even larger.
那他的胜利就更加伟大了
Minstrels will write songs about him.
歌手会写歌歌颂他的
Okay, how about this?
I'll do the talking.
好了 这样吧? 我来谈
You just stand behind me
and try to look formidable.
你们就站我后边 装的吓人一点
I should've peed before we left.
出门前该先尿一泡的
Yeah?
什么事?
- Hi, Kurt.
- Lenny, right?
- 嗨 Kurt
- Lenny 对吧?
I don't really go by
Lenny, but that's okay.
我不喜欢人叫我Lenny 但也行啦
Um, you remember
Sheldon, Howard and Raj.
记得吗 他们是Sheldon Howard和Raj
No. What do you want?
不记得 你有什么事?
You don't remember me? How
could he not remember me?
你不记得我了? 他怎么会不记得我呢?
Sheldon, not now.
Sheldon 不是时候
I remember him.
我可记得他
Okay, here it is.Penny's
in kind of a financial jam,
好的 是这样 Penny有点经济困难
and the money that you owe her would
go a long way to solving her problems.
你欠她的那些钱可以解决她的难题
And she sent you to get it from me?
她派你来讨债的?
No, no, she's too proud
to ask for the money.
不不 她放不下架子来要钱
I, on the other hand, feel
you should honor your debt.
我呢 则觉得你欠债应该还钱
You do?
你这么想哈?
Feel is a kind of a...
it's a strong word.
"觉得"这词其实...是很强烈一词
Um, I just think it would be
a nice gesture on your part.
我认为这样做对你也好
She'll get it when she gets it.
该还她时自然给她了
Well, there you go. Problem solved.
得 问题解决了
A successful quest. Now let's go find
a gas station with a clean bathroom.
探险成功 咱现在去找个
带干净卫生间的加油站吧
No, the problem isn't
soed. He just ew uoff.
不行 还没解决 他根本没往心里去
********
知道了 他不认得我是因为
上次见面时我穿的是万圣节衣服
Come on, Leonard, let'go
好了 Leonard 走吧
NoYou can leave if you want
to. I'gonna see this through.
不走 要走你走 我要搞搞清楚
Okay.
好吧
I guess, technically, that was my fault.
我想 应该是我的错
I'm not leaving here
without Penny's money.
拿不回Penny的钱我就不走
What happened to your backup?
你的后援团呢?
I don't need backup.
我不需要后援
I have right on my side.
正义站在我这边
And I'm wearing cargo
shorts under my pants.
我裤子里穿的是休闲短裤
Congratulations.
恭喜
You may not have
succeeded in getting cash,
或许你没能成功拿到现金
but you did secure a formal
acknowledgment of the debt.
但你拿到了正式的欠债书
Maybe we should have
your head notarized.
或许我们该拿你脑袋去认证一下
If anybody cares, I still have to pee.
各位行行好 我还是得尿尿
- Is Sheldon here?
- Yeah. Hang on. Sheldon!
- Sheldon在吗?
- 嗯 等会 Sheldon!
Nice hat.
帽子不错
It's kind of a fashionable
look these days.
最近流行这造型
Maybe if you're working on a tuna boat.
要是在渔船工作差不多
Hello, Penny.
你好啊 Penny
Sheldon, here is your money. Thank
you very much. It helped a lot.
Sheldon 这是你的钱 太感谢了
帮了我大忙
Sarcasm?
反话?
No.
不是
Darn. I can't seem to
get the hang of that.
讨厌 我咋就掌握不好呢
Hey, I know it's none of my business,
but where did the money come from?
嘿 虽然不关我的事
还是想问问钱哪来的?
Well, I cut back my expenses like you said and
picked up a few more hours at the restaurant,
我像你说的那样节省开支
在餐馆多加了几个小时的班
but the biggest thing was, out of the blue,
Kurt shows up and gives me the money he owes me.
但最重要的是 Kurt突然出现
把欠我的钱都还给我了
Really? Did he say why?
真的啊? 说为啥了没?
Yes, he said he was feeling guilty
and wanted to do what was right.
说了 他说他很有愧疚感 想做对的事
That's it?
就这样?
Did he give any reason as to why
he came to this moral epiphany?
他有没说怎么就突然有道德觉悟了?
Nope. I just think he's really changed.
没 我觉得他是真的变了
We're having dinner tomorrow night,
and I get to wear my new beret.
我们明晚要一起吃饭
我要戴新贝雷帽了
Bye, guys.
再见 伙计
Bye.
拜
Well done, Leonard.
干得好啊 Leonard
The true hero doesn't seek adulation.
真正的英雄不求恭维
He fights for right and justice
simply because it's his nature.
出于本性为正义和公平而战
Penny's hooking up with her jerk of an ex-boyfriend
and I have indelible ink on my forehead!
Penny和混蛋前男友勾搭上了
我脑门还写着大大的墨水字!
That's your badge of honor--
your warrior's wound, if you will.
这是你的荣誉勋章啊
你的战士伤痕 你同意的话
I was wrong.
我错了
Minstrels will write songs about you.
歌手会写歌来歌颂你啊
Great.
大好
* There once was a
brave lad named Leonard *
* 曾有一位勇敢的青年
他的名字叫做Leonard *
* With a -fi
fiddle dee-dee *
* 满嘴跑火车 逞英雄 *
* He faced a fearsome giant *
* 他与可怕巨人对峙 *
* While Raj just wanted to pee.*
* 而Raj却只想嘘嘘 *
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
-天才理论传
第二季 第14集 完